good morning prudential at prudential
uganda
we believe that constant training
creates an efficient agency force
you are special and will receive the
tools needed to succeed
as thousands have done before you
prudential has
500 000 representatives just like you
across the world
serving 20 million customers worldwide
we know how to support your growth
and we have experience in doing so for
nearly 200 years
our rookie development program
accelerates development of new agents by
instilling in their key professional
selling skills
while inspiring them to embrace a
rewarding career
in insurance sales while our team leader
development program
helps you attain vital leadership skills
needed to effectively
coach and motivate agency teams to build
their business
our continuous development program
ensures that we continuously
improve the skills of our agency
leadership and sales agents to be
distinct
in the industry welcome to a world of
opportunity
welcome to prudential